

# FIND ME ONLINE

#### in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sveto slav-yordanov003/

#### GitHub

https://github.com/yordanov03

#### Web Card

https://yordanov03.github.io/

## **LANGUAGES**

English Proficient •••••

German Advanced •••••

# **SKILLS**

C# · SQL · Javascript · Typescript ·

HTML5 · CSS · Mongodb · .NetCore ·

ASP.NET · .NetFramework · Angular ·

Git · Azure · Docker · Kubernetes ·

 $CI/CD \cdot Microservices \cdot Bitbucket \cdot$ 

Azure Devops

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Wohngeld Go**

2020 - 2021 Hamburg, Germany

#### Link

 State projects aimed at providing financial aid for housing commodities

### **DSK** bank

2020 - 2020 Sofia, Bulgaria <u>Link</u>

• System for tracking legal cases for the largest national bank in Bulgaria

# NOTABLE CERTIFICATION

Microsoft certified - AZ-900

Azure fundamentals

# Svetoslav Yordanov

# Web Developer

\$\oldsymbol{0}\$ 076 697 22 20 @ svetoslav.yordanov.003@gmail.com 
\$\oldsymbol{V}\$ Zurich, Switzerland

#### SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with several years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Full Stack Developer

2022 - 2022

#### Credit Suisse AG

Wroclaw, Poland

- Creation of web tools with .NetCore, Angular and SQL of significant matter for the decision-making for future investments
- Proactively involved in the **full lifecycle** of tools for process **automation**
- Developing optimizations and cost-effectiveness via creating custom-tailored tools according to the needs of the business
- Cloud application development and migration

# Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022

#### Freelancer

Berlin, Germany

- Design, implementation and deployment of tools as per customer specifications
- . Monolith or microservices architecture based in cloud environment
- Integration of third party applications (Dynatrace, Keypay, Mailchimp etc.)
- Performing root cause analysis to identify bugs and roll out fixes to production

# Software Developer

2020 - 2021

### thinfabrics Gmbh - Bulpros consulting

Hamburg, Germany

- Lead Developer, participating actively decision-making concerning tech stack and deployment
- Developing new features and integration with existing services for state project, aimed at providing financial aid for housing commodities
- Refactor legacy code and update internal customer framework
- Due to timely project completion, the development of 7 more projects was entrusted to us by the same costumer

### Web Developer

2018 - 2020

### **Hewlett Packard Enterprise**

Sofia, Bulgaria

Sofia, Bulgaria

- Diversified the team's **technologies portfolio** by bringing years of accumulated knowledge and experience in .Net
- Undertook a 1200 tables SQL database redesign and revamped the tech stack
- Wrote and optimized legacy code for data and processing heavy tasks automation
- Designed and developed reusable software portals for 3 metrics, improving data accuracy and reducing reporting efforts

# **EDUCATION**

Web developer 2017 - 2019
Software university Sofia, Bulgaria

Masters degree in Marketing and 2015 - 2017
communications

University of National and World Economy

International Relations 2008 - 2012
University of National and World Economy Sofia, Bulgaria